{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "question": "America Online (AOL) started out as which of these online service providers?",
        "correct_answer": "Quantum Link",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "CompuServe",
          "Prodigy",
          "GEnie"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "False"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Which of these is not a world in the anime &quot;Buddyfight&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Ancient Dragon World",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Dragon World",
          "Star Dragon World",
          "Darkness Dragon World"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "False"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a playable character race in the video game &quot;Starbound&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Fenerox",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Floran",
          "Novakid",
          "Hylotl"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which English guitarist has the nickname &quot;Slowhand&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Eric Clapton",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Mark Knopfler",
          "Jeff Beck",
          "Jimmy Page"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "question": "The &#039;Raspberry Pi&#039; series of single-board computers were created in the United States.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In &quot;Puella Magi Madoka Magica&quot;, what is the first name of Madoka&#039;s younger brother?",
        "correct_answer": "Tatsuya",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Montoya",
          "Tomohisa",
          "Minato"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }